Voting is a privilege
in this country
and you need to be legal, not
like California with three
million alleles vote with it.
Let’s talk about that.
I’m glad I brought
that up that true.
So we’re you getting your
information from the media.
Well, I wish the
media some of it.
But CNN I believe, of the
three million illegal people
voted well it was kind
of all across the media.
Well, first it was CNN didn’t
do it then they were being smart
this time.
Do you think that
$3 million illegal.
I believe in
California that they
were alleles that vote, then.
I don’t to tell you truth.
Nobody really knows that either.
But do you think three
dozen or do you think three.
I think there was a good amount
because the president told
people that they could vote.
And it happened in Nashua.
We got some people that they
wanted to nashe when they said
the president said, I can vote.
I’m here illegally.
You hear President Obama
say that illegal people
could be right or wrong.
So did he ever tell me
where now you could find it.
Google it.
You can find it on Facebook.
All right hold on.
I don’t want to
waste any more time.
But anyway, I see
where it came from.
And it’s a Fox Business
Network deceptively
edited a clip of Barack Obama
to argue that the president
encourages illegal immigrants
to vote when in fact, he
said nothing of the sort.
When you go back to the
transcript you as you
sit here today.
Think that millions of illegal
people voted in this country.
You believe that there was
widespread voting abuse.
I think there was in some states
in the millions of people.
I California allows that
people to not allow the legal.
You mean delete.
You mean voter fraud.
California allows.
I believe there was voter
fraud in this country.